Translator: Joseph Geni
Reviewer: Morton Bast
译者：Joseph Geni
审稿人：Morton Bast
So I want to start by offering you
a free no-tech life hack,
所以我想首先为您提供
一个免费的无技术生活窍门，
and all it requires of you is this:
它所要求的就是：
that you change your posture
for two minutes.
您改变姿势
两分钟。
But before I give it away,
I want to ask you to right now
但在我透露之前，
我想请您现在对
do a little audit of your body
and what you're doing with your body.
您的身体
以及您对身体所做的事情进行一些检查。
So how many of you are
sort of making yourselves smaller?
那么，你们中有多少人在
某种程度上让自己变得更小呢？
Maybe you're hunching, crossing your legs,
maybe wrapping your ankles.
也许你弯腰驼背，交叉双腿，
也许包裹着脚踝。
Sometimes we hold onto our arms like this.
有时我们会像这样握住手臂。
Sometimes we spread out. (Laughter)
有时我们分散开来。  （笑声）
I see you.
我看到你了。
So I want you to pay attention
to what you're doing right now.
所以我希望你注意
你现在正在做的事情。
We're going to come back
to that in a few minutes,
我们将
在几分钟后回到这个问题，
and I'm hoping that if you learn
to tweak this a little bit,
我希望如果你学会
稍微调整一下，
it could significantly change
the way your life unfolds.
它可以显着改变
你的生活展开方式。
So, we're really fascinated
with body language,
所以，我们真的
对肢体语言着迷，
and we're particularly interested
in other people's body language.
而且
对其他人的肢体语言特别感兴趣。
You know, we're interested in,
like, you know — (Laughter) —
你知道，我们感兴趣的是，
比如，你知道——（笑声）——
an awkward interaction, or a smile,
尴尬的互动，或者一个微笑，
or a contemptuous glance,
or maybe a very awkward wink,
或者一个轻蔑的眼神，
或者一个非常尴尬的眨眼，
or maybe even something like a handshake.
或者甚至是握手之类的东西。
Narrator: Here they are
arriving at Number 10.
旁白：他们
到达了 10 号。
This lucky policeman gets to shake hands
with the President of the United States.
这位幸运的警察可以
与美国总统握手。
Here comes the Prime Minister --
No. (Laughter) (Applause)
总理来了 -
不。（笑声）（掌声）
(Laughter) (Applause)
（笑声）（掌声）
Amy Cuddy: So a handshake,
or the lack of a handshake,
Amy Cuddy：所以一次握手，
或者不握手，
can have us talking for weeks
and weeks and weeks.
可以让我们谈论数周
、数周、数周。
Even the BBC and The New York Times.
甚至 BBC 和纽约时报。
So obviously when we think
about nonverbal behavior,
显然，当我们
考虑非语言行为
or body language -- but we call it
nonverbals as social scientists --
或肢体语言时——但我们
作为社会科学家称之为非语言——
it's language, so we think
about communication.
它是语言，所以我们考虑
的是沟通。
When we think about communication,
we think about interactions.
当我们考虑沟通时，
我们会考虑互动。
So what is your body language
communicating to me?
那么你的肢体语言在
向我传达什么信息呢？
What's mine communicating to you?
我在跟你传达什么信息？
And there's a lot of reason to believe
that this is a valid way to look at this.
有很多理由相信
这是看待这个问题的有效方法。
So social scientists
have spent a lot of time
因此，社会科学家
花了很多时间
looking at the effects
of our body language,
研究
我们的肢体语言
or other people's body language,
on judgments.
或其他人的肢体语言
对判断的影响。
And we make sweeping judgments
and inferences from body language.
我们根据肢体语言做出全面的判断
和推论。
And those judgments can predict
really meaningful life outcomes
这些判断可以预测
真正有意义的生活结果，
like who we hire or promote,
who we ask out on a date.
例如我们雇用或晋升谁，
我们约谁出去约会。
For example, Nalini Ambady,
a researcher at Tufts University,
例如，塔夫茨大学的研究员纳里尼·安巴迪（Nalini Ambady）
shows that when people watch
30-second soundless clips
表明，当人们观看
30 秒
of real physician-patient interactions,
真实医患互动的无声片段时，
their judgments
of the physician's niceness
他们对
医生友善的判断
predict whether or not
that physician will be sued.
可以预测
该医生是否会被起诉。
So it doesn't have to do so much
因此，这
with whether or not that physician
was incompetent,
与该医生是否无能没有太大关系
，
but do we like that person
and how they interacted?
但我们是否喜欢那个人
以及他们如何互动？
Even more dramatic,
Alex Todorov at Princeton
更戏剧性的是，
普林斯顿大学的亚历克斯·托多罗夫（Alex Todorov）
has shown us that judgments
of political candidates' faces
向我们展示了，只需一秒钟
对政治候选人面孔的判断就可以
in just one second predict 70 percent
预测
of U.S. Senate and gubernatorial
race outcomes,
美国参议院和州长
竞选结果的 70%，
and even, let's go digital,
甚至，让我们走向数字化，
emoticons used well in online negotiations
在线谈判中使用得当的表情符号
can lead you to claim more value
from that negotiation.
可以让你 从谈判中获得更多价值
。
If you use them poorly, bad idea. Right?
如果你使用不当，那是个坏主意。 正确的？
So when we think of nonverbals,
we think of how we judge others,
因此，当我们想到非语言时，
我们会想到我们如何评价他人，
how they judge us
and what the outcomes are.
他们如何评价我们
以及结果是什么。
We tend to forget, though,
the other audience
然而，我们往往会忘记受
that's influenced by our nonverbals,
and that's ourselves.
我们的非语言影响的其他观众，
那就是我们自己。
We are also influenced by our nonverbals,
我们还受到我们的非语言、
our thoughts and our feelings
and our physiology.
我们的思想、我们的感受
和我们的生理的影响。
So what nonverbals am I talking about?
那么我在谈论什么非语言呢？
I'm a social psychologist.
I study prejudice,
我是一名社会心理学家。
我研究偏见，
and I teach at a competitive
business school,
在一所竞争激烈的
商学院任教，
so it was inevitable that I would become
interested in power dynamics.
所以我不可避免地会对
权力动态产生兴趣。
I became especially interested
in nonverbal expressions
我
对
of power and dominance.
权力和统治力的非语言表达特别感兴趣。
And what are nonverbal expressions
of power and dominance?
什么是
权力和统治力的非语言表达？
Well, this is what they are.
嗯，这就是他们的本质。
So in the animal kingdom,
they are about expanding.
所以在动物王国里，
它们是在扩张。
So you make yourself big, you stretch out,
所以你让自己变得更大，你伸展，
you take up space,
you're basically opening up.
你占据空间，
你基本上是在开放。
It's about opening up.
这是关于开放。
And this is true
across the animal kingdom.
在整个动物王国都是如此。
It's not just limited to primates.
它不仅限于灵长类动物。
And humans do the same thing. (Laughter)
人类也做同样的事情。  （笑声）
So they do this both when they have
power sort of chronically,
所以，当他们
长期拥有权力时，
and also when they're feeling
powerful in the moment.
以及当他们
当下感觉强大时，他们都会这样做。
And this one is especially interesting
because it really shows us
这一点特别有趣，
因为它确实向我们展示了
how universal and old these
expressions of power are.
这些
权力表达方式是多么普遍和古老。 杰西卡·特蕾西研究过
This expression, which is known as pride,
这种被称为骄傲的表达方式
Jessica Tracy has studied.
。
She shows that people
who are born with sight
她表明，
天生有视力的人和
and people who are congenitally
blind do this
先天失明的人
when they win at a physical competition.
在体育比赛中获胜时都会这样做。
So when they cross
the finish line and they've won,
因此，当他们冲过
终点线并获胜时，
it doesn't matter if they've never
seen anyone do it.
即使他们从未
见过有人这样做也没关系。
They do this.
他们这样做。
So the arms up in the V,
the chin is slightly lifted.
所以双臂向上呈V字形，
下巴微微抬起。
What do we do when we feel powerless?
当我们感到无能为力时，我们该怎么办？
We do exactly the opposite.
我们的做法恰恰相反。
We close up.
We wrap ourselves up.
我们关闭。
我们把自己包裹起来。
We make ourselves small.
我们让自己变得渺小。
We don't want to bump
into the person next to us.
我们不想
撞到旁边的人。
So again, both animals and humans
do the same thing.
同样，动物和人类都
做同样的事情。
And this is what happens
when you put together high and low power.
这就是
当你将高功率和低功率放在一起时会发生的情况。
So what we tend to
do when it comes to power
因此，
当涉及到权力时，我们倾向于做的
is that we complement
the other's nonverbals.
就是补充
对方的非语言能力。
So if someone is being
really powerful with us,
因此，如果有人
对我们非常强大，
we tend to make ourselves smaller.
We don't mirror them.
我们就会倾向于让自己变得更渺小。
我们不镜像他们。
We do the opposite of them.
我们做的与他们相反。
So I'm watching this behavior
in the classroom,
那么我
在教室里观察这种行为，
and what do I notice?
我注意到了什么？
I notice that MBA students really exhibit
the full range of power nonverbals.
我注意到 MBA 学生确实展现出了
全方位的非语言能力。
So you have people
who are like caricatures of alphas,
因此，有些人
就像漫画中的阿尔法，
really coming into the room, they get
right into the middle of the room
真正进入房间，他们甚至在上课之前就
进入房间的中间
before class even starts,
like they really want to occupy space.
，
就像他们真的想占据空间一样。
When they sit down,
they're sort of spread out.
当他们坐下时，
他们会分散开来。
They raise their hands like this.
他们像这样举起手来。 还有
You have other people
who are virtually collapsing
一些人进来时
几乎崩溃了
when they come in.
As soon they come in, you see it.
。
他们一进来，你就看到了。
You see it on their faces
and their bodies,
你可以在他们的脸上和身体上看到这一点
，
and they sit in their chair
and they make themselves tiny,
他们坐在椅子上，
把自己变得很小，
and they go like this
when they raise their hand.
当他们举起手时，他们就是这样。
I notice a couple of things about this.
我注意到有关于此的一些事情。
One, you're not going to be surprised.
第一，你不会感到惊讶。
It seems to be related to gender.
好像和性别有关。
So women are much more likely
to do this kind of thing than men.
所以女性
比男性更容易做这种事情。
Women feel chronically
less powerful than men,
女性长期感觉自己
不如男性强大，
so this is not surprising.
所以这并不奇怪。
But the other thing I noticed
但我注意到的另一件事
is that it also seemed
to be related to the extent
是，这似乎也
与
to which the students were participating,
and how well they were participating.
学生参与的程度
以及参与的程度有关。
And this is really important
in the MBA classroom,
这
在 MBA 课堂上非常重要，
because participation
counts for half the grade.
因为参与
度占成绩的一半。
So business schools have been struggling
with this gender grade gap.
因此，商学院一直在努力解决
这种性别成绩差距。
You get these equally qualified
women and men coming in
你让这些同等资格的
女性和男性进来，
and then you get
these differences in grades,
然后你就会发现
成绩上的差异，
and it seems to be partly
attributable to participation.
这似乎部分
归因于参与。
So I started to wonder, you know, okay,
所以我开始想，你知道，好吧，
so you have these people coming in
like this, and they're participating.
所以你让这些人像
这样进来，他们正在参与。
Is it possible that we could
get people to fake it
我们是否有可能
让人们伪造它
and would it lead them
to participate more?
并会导致他们
更多地参与？
So my main collaborator
Dana Carney, who's at Berkeley,
所以我的主要合作者
达纳·卡尼（Dana Carney）在伯克利大学，
and I really wanted to know,
can you fake it till you make it?
我真的很想知道，
你能假装它直到你成功吗？
Like, can you do this
just for a little while
比如，你能这样做
一段时间，
and actually experience
a behavioral outcome
并真正体验到
that makes you seem more powerful?
让你看起来更强大的行为结果吗？
So we know that our nonverbals
govern how other people
所以我们知道，我们的非语言行为
决定着其他人
think and feel about us.
There's a lot of evidence.
对我们的看法和感受。
有很多证据。
But our question really was,
但我们真正的问题是，
do our nonverbals govern
how we think and feel about ourselves?
我们的非语言行为是否决定了
我们对自己的思考和感受？
There's some evidence that they do.
有一些证据表明他们确实这样做。
So, for example, we smile
when we feel happy,
所以，举例来说，
当我们感到快乐时，我们会微笑，
but also, when we're forced to smile
而且，当我们像这样用牙齿叼着笔被迫微笑时
by holding a pen in our teeth
like this, it makes us feel happy.
，也会让我们感到快乐。
So it goes both ways.
所以这是双向的。
When it comes to power,
it also goes both ways.
当谈到权力时，
它也是双向的。
So when you feel powerful,
因此，当你感觉自己很强大时，
you're more likely to do this,
你就更有可能这样做，
but it's also possible
that when you pretend to be powerful,
但也有可能
当你假装很强大时，
you are more likely
to actually feel powerful.
你更有可能
真正感到自己很强大。
So the second question
really was, you know,
所以第二个问题
确实是，你知道，
so we know that our minds
change our bodies,
所以我们知道我们的思想会
改变我们的身体，
but is it also true
that our bodies change our minds?
但是
我们的身体也会改变我们的思想吗？
And when I say minds,
in the case of the powerful,
当我说思想时，
就强者而言，
what am I talking about?
我在说什么？
So I'm talking about thoughts and feelings
所以我谈论的是思想和感受，
and the sort of physiological things
that make up our thoughts and feelings,
以及
构成我们的思想和感受的生理因素，就
and in my case, that's hormones.
I look at hormones.
我而言，这就是荷尔蒙。
我看荷尔蒙。
So what do the minds of the powerful
versus the powerless look like?
那么，强者与弱者的思想是什么
样的呢？ 毫不奇怪，
So powerful people tend to be,
not surprisingly,
如此强大的人往往会更加自信、
more assertive and more confident,
more optimistic.
更加自信、
更加乐观。
They actually feel they're going to win
even at games of chance.
他们实际上觉得
即使在机会游戏中他们也会获胜。
They also tend to be able
to think more abstractly.
他们也往往能够进行
更抽象的思考。
So there are a lot of differences.
They take more risks.
所以有很多差异。
他们承担更多的风险。
There are a lot of differences
between powerful and powerless people.
有权力的人和无权力的人之间有很多区别。 从
Physiologically,
there also are differences
生理学角度来看，
on two key hormones: testosterone,
which is the dominance hormone,
两种关键激素也存在差异：睾酮（
主导激素）
and cortisol, which is the stress hormone.
和皮质醇（应激激素）。
So what we find is that high-power
alpha males in primate hierarchies
所以我们发现，
灵长类动物等级中的高权力雄性领袖
have high testosterone and low cortisol,
具有高睾酮和低皮质醇，
and powerful and effective leaders
而强大而有效的领导者
also have high testosterone
and low cortisol.
也具有高睾酮
和低皮质醇。
So what does that mean?
When you think about power,
那么这是什么意思呢？
当你想到权力时，
people tended to think
only about testosterone,
人们往往
只想到睾丸激素，
because that was about dominance.
因为那意味着统治地位。
But really, power is also about
how you react to stress.
但实际上，力量还在于
你如何应对压力。
So do you want the high-power
leader that's dominant,
那么，你想要一个高权力的
领导者吗？他具有主导地位，
high on testosterone,
but really stress reactive?
睾丸激素水平高，
但对压力非常敏感？
Probably not, right?
可能不会，对吧？
You want the person who's powerful
and assertive and dominant,
你想要的是一个有力量
、自信、有统治力的人，
but not very stress reactive,
the person who's laid back.
但又不太容易受到压力影响，是一个
悠闲的人。
So we know that in primate hierarchies,
所以我们知道，在灵长类等级制度中，
if an alpha needs to take over,
如果一个阿尔法需要接管，
if an individual needs to take over
an alpha role sort of suddenly,
如果一个个体需要
突然接管阿尔法角色，
within a few days,
that individual's testosterone has gone up
在几天之内，
该个体的睾丸激素会
significantly and his cortisol
has dropped significantly.
显着上升，而他的皮质醇
会显着下降。
So we have this evidence,
both that the body can shape
所以我们有证据表明，
身体可以塑造
the mind, at least at the facial level,
心灵，至少在面部层面，
and also that role changes
can shape the mind.
而且角色的变化也
可以塑造心灵。
So what happens, okay,
you take a role change,
那么会发生什么，好吧，
你进行角色改变，
what happens if you do that
at a really minimal level,
如果你
在一个非常小的水平上这样做，
like this tiny manipulation,
this tiny intervention?
比如这种微小的操纵，
这种微小的干预，会发生什么？
"For two minutes," you say,
"I want you to stand like this,
“两分钟，”你说，
“我希望你像这样站着，
and it's going to make you feel
more powerful."
这会让你感觉
更有力量。”
So this is what we did.
这就是我们所做的。
We decided to bring people into the lab
and run a little experiment,
我们决定带人们进入实验室
并进行一个小实验，
and these people adopted, for two minutes,
这些人在两分钟内采用了
either high-power poses
or low-power poses,
高功率姿势
或低功率姿势，
and I'm just going to show
you five of the poses,
我将向
您展示其中五个姿势，
although they took on only two.
尽管它们 只承担了两个。
So here's one.
所以这是一个。 还有
A couple more.
几个。
This one has been dubbed
the "Wonder Woman" by the media.
这位被
媒体称为“神奇女侠”的人。
Here are a couple more.
这里还有一些。
So you can be standing
or you can be sitting.
所以你可以站着，
也可以坐着。
And here are the low-power poses.
这是低功率姿势。
So you're folding up,
you're making yourself small.
所以你折叠起来，
你让自己变小。
This one is very low-power.
这个功率非常低。
When you're touching your neck,
you're really protecting yourself.
当你触摸自己的脖子时，
你实际上是在保护自己。
So this is what happens.
所以这就是发生的事情。
They come in, they spit into a vial,
他们进来，向小瓶吐口水，
for two minutes, we say,
"You need to do this or this."
持续两分钟，我们说，
“你需要这样做或这样做。”
They don't look at pictures of the poses.
他们不看姿势照片。
We don't want to prime them
with a concept of power.
我们不想让他们灌输
权力概念。
We want them to be feeling power.
我们希望他们感受到力量。
So two minutes they do this.
他们这样做了两分钟。
We then ask them, "How powerful
do you feel?" on a series of items,
然后我们问他们：“
你觉得自己有多强大？” 在一系列项目上，
and then we give them
an opportunity to gamble,
然后我们给他们
一个赌博的机会，
and then we take another saliva sample.
然后我们又采集了另一个唾液样本。
That's it. That's the whole experiment.
就是这样。 这就是整个实验。
So this is what we find.
这就是我们发现的。
Risk tolerance, which is the gambling,
风险承受能力，也就是赌博，
we find that when you are
in the high-power pose condition,
我们发现当你
处于高权力姿势的时候，
86 percent of you will gamble.
86%的人会赌博。
When you're in the low-power
pose condition,
当你处于低功率
姿势状态时，
only 60 percent, and that's
a whopping significant difference.
只有 60%，这是
一个巨大的显着差异。
Here's what we find on testosterone.
这是我们在睾酮方面的发现。
From their baseline when they come in,
从他们进来时的基线来看，
high-power people experience
about a 20-percent increase,
高权力的人经历了
大约 20% 的增长，
and low-power people experience
about a 10-percent decrease.
而低权力的人经历了
大约 10% 的下降。
So again, two minutes,
and you get these changes.
再说一遍，两分钟，
你就会得到这些变化。
Here's what you get on cortisol.
这就是你从皮质醇中得到的结果。
High-power people experience
about a 25-percent decrease,
高权力的人经历了
大约 25% 的减少，
and the low-power people experience
about a 15-percent increase.
而低权力的人经历了
大约 15% 的增加。
So two minutes lead
to these hormonal changes
因此，两分钟会
导致荷尔蒙发生变化，使
that configure your brain
您的大脑
to basically be either assertive,
confident and comfortable,
基本上变得自信、
自信和舒适，
or really stress-reactive,
and feeling sort of shut down.
或者真正对压力敏感，
感觉有点封闭。
And we've all had the feeling, right?
我们都有过这种感觉，对吧？
So it seems that our nonverbals do govern
how we think and feel about ourselves,
所以看来我们的非语言确实控制着
我们对自己的思考和感受，
so it's not just others,
but it's also ourselves.
所以这不仅是别人的，
也是我们自己的。
Also, our bodies change our minds.
此外，我们的身体会改变我们的想法。
But the next question, of course,
但下一个问题当然
is, can power posing for a few minutes
是，几分钟的强力姿势真的能
really change your life
in meaningful ways?
以有意义的方式改变你的生活吗？
This is in the lab, it's this little task,
it's just a couple of minutes.
这是在实验室里，这是一个小任务，
只需几分钟。
Where can you actually apply this?
你可以在哪里实际应用这个？
Which we cared about, of course.
当然，我们关心这一点。
And so we think where you want to use this
is evaluative situations,
因此，我们认为您想要在
评估情况下使用它，
like social threat situations.
例如社会威胁情况。 您的朋友在
Where are you being evaluated,
either by your friends?
哪里对您进行评价
？
For teenagers,
it's at the lunchroom table.
对于青少年来说，
它是在午餐桌上。
For some people it's speaking
at a school board meeting.
对于某些人来说，这是
在学校董事会会议上的讲话。
It might be giving a pitch
or giving a talk like this
它可能是进行推销
或进行这样的演讲
or doing a job interview.
或进行工作面试。
We decided that the one
that most people could relate to
我们决定，
大多数人都可以理解的面试就是工作面试，
because most people had been through,
was the job interview.
因为大多数人都经历过
。
So we published these findings,
所以我们发表了这些发现，
and the media are all over it,
媒体都在关注它，
and they say, Okay, so this is what you do
他们说，好吧，这就是
when you go in
for the job interview, right?
你参加
工作面试时要做的，对吗？
(Laughter)
（笑声）
You know, so we were of course
horrified, and said,
你知道，所以我们当然感到
震惊，并说，
Oh my God, no,
that's not what we meant at all.
天哪，不，
我们根本不是这个意思。
For numerous reasons, no, don't do that.
由于多种原因，不，不要这样做。
Again, this is not about you
talking to other people.
再说一遍，这不是你
与其他人交谈的问题。 这
It's you talking to yourself.
是你自言自语。 在
What do you do before you go
into a job interview? You do this.
参加工作面试之前你会做什么
？ 你做这个。
You're sitting down.
You're looking at your iPhone --
你坐下了。
您正在查看您的 iPhone
or your Android, not trying
to leave anyone out.
或 Android，而不是试图将
任何人排除在外。
You're looking at your notes,
你正在看你的笔记，
you're hunching up, making yourself small,
你弯腰驼背，让自己变得渺小，而
when really what you should
be doing maybe is this,
你真正应该
做的也许是这样，
like, in the bathroom, right?
Do that. Find two minutes.
比如，在浴室里，对吧？
去做。 找两分钟。
So that's what we want to test. Okay?
这就是我们想要测试的。 好的？
So we bring people into a lab,
所以我们把人们带进实验室，
and they do either high-
or low-power poses again,
他们再次摆出高权力
或低权力的姿势，
they go through
a very stressful job interview.
他们经历了
非常紧张的工作面试。
It's five minutes long.
They are being recorded.
它有五分钟长。
他们正在被记录。
They're being judged also,
他们也在接受评判，
and the judges are trained
to give no nonverbal feedback,
评委们接受过
不提供非语言反馈的培训，
so they look like this.
所以他们看起来像这样。
Imagine this is the person
interviewing you.
想象一下这是
面试你的人。
So for five minutes, nothing,
and this is worse than being heckled.
五分钟之内，什么也没有，
这比被质问更糟糕。
People hate this.
人们讨厌这个。
It's what Marianne LaFrance calls
"standing in social quicksand."
这就是玛丽安·拉弗朗斯所说的
“站在社会流沙中”。
So this really spikes your cortisol.
所以这确实会刺激你的皮质醇。
So this is the job interview
we put them through,
这就是
我们对他们进行的面试，
because we really wanted
to see what happened.
因为我们真的想
看看发生了什么。
We then have these coders look
at these tapes, four of them.
然后我们让这些编码员查看
这些磁带，共四盘。
They're blind to the hypothesis.
They're blind to the conditions.
他们对这个假设视而不见。
他们对条件视而不见。
They have no idea
who's been posing in what pose,
他们不知道
谁摆出了什么姿势，
and they end up looking
at these sets of tapes,
最后他们看了
这些录像带，
and they say,
"We want to hire these people,"
然后说，
“我们想雇用这些人”，
all the high-power posers.
所有这些人都是高权力的摆姿势者。
"We don't want to hire these people.
“我们不想雇用这些人。
We also evaluate these people
much more positively overall."
我们对这些人的总体评价也
更加积极。”
But what's driving it?
但是什么推动了它呢？
It's not about the content of the speech.
这与演讲的内容无关。
It's about the presence
that they're bringing to the speech.
这是关于
他们在演讲中的表现。
Because we rate them
on all these variables
因为我们根据与
related to competence,
like, how well-structured is the speech?
能力相关的所有这些变量对他们进行评分，
例如演讲的结构如何？
How good is it?
What are their qualifications?
有多好？
他们有什么资格？
No effect on those things.
This is what's affected.
对那些东西没有影响。
这就是受到影响的。
These kinds of things.
诸如此类的事情。 基本上，
People are bringing
their true selves, basically.
人们正在展现
真实的自己。
They're bringing themselves.
他们自己带来。
They bring their ideas, but as themselves,
他们带来了自己的想法，但就像他们自己一样，
with no, you know, residue over them.
你知道，没有任何残留。
So this is what's driving the effect,
or mediating the effect.
所以这就是驱动效应
或调节效应的因素。
So when I tell people about this,
因此，当我告诉人们这一点时，
that our bodies change our minds
and our minds can change our behavior,
我们的身体改变我们的思想
，我们的思想可以改变我们的行为，
and our behavior can change
our outcomes, they say to me,
我们的行为可以改变
我们的结果，他们对我说，
"It feels fake." Right?
“这感觉很假。” 正确的？
So I said, fake it till you make it.
所以我说，假装它直到你成功为止。
It's not me.
这不是我。
I don't want to get there
and then still feel like a fraud.
我不想到了那里
之后仍然感觉自己像个骗子。
I don't want to feel like an impostor.
我不想感觉自己像个骗子。
I don't want to get there only to feel
like I'm not supposed to be here.
我不想到了那里只是
觉得我不应该在这里。
And that really resonated with me,
这确实引起了我的共鸣，
because I want to tell you
a little story about being an impostor
因为我想告诉你
一个关于作为冒名顶替者的小故事，
and feeling like
I'm not supposed to be here.
并且感觉
我不应该在这里。
When I was 19, I was
in a really bad car accident.
当我19岁的时候，我
遭遇了一场严重的车祸。
I was thrown out of a car,
rolled several times.
我被从车里扔了出来，
滚了好几圈。
I was thrown from the car.
我被从车上扔了下去。
And I woke up in a head injury rehab ward,
我在头部受伤康复病房醒来，
and I had been withdrawn from college,
我已经从大学退学了，
and I learned that my IQ had dropped
by two standard deviations,
我得知我的智商下降了
两个标准差，
which was very traumatic.
这是非常痛苦的。
I knew my IQ because
I had identified with being smart,
我知道自己的智商，因为
我认为自己很聪明，
and I had been called gifted as a child.
小时候就被称为天才。
So I'm taken out of college,
I keep trying to go back.
所以我从大学退学了，
我一直在努力回去。
They say, "You're not going
to finish college.
他们说：“你不会
完成大学学业。
Just, you know, there are other
things for you to do,
只是，你知道，
你还有其他事情要做，
but that's not going to work out for you."
但这对你来说是行不通的。”
So I really struggled
with this, and I have to say,
所以我真的很挣扎
，我不得不说，
having your identity taken
from you, your core identity,
你的身份被剥夺了
，你的核心身份被剥夺了，
and for me it was being smart,
对我来说这是明智的，
having that taken from you,
失去了你的身份，
there's nothing that leaves you feeling
more powerless than that.
没有什么比这更让你感到
无能为力了。
So I felt entirely powerless.
所以我感到完全无能为力。
I worked and worked, and I got lucky,
我工作又工作，我很幸运，我
and worked, and got lucky, and worked.
工作，我很幸运，我工作。
Eventually I graduated from college.
最终我大学毕业了。
It took me four years
longer than my peers,
我
比同龄人多花了四年时间，
and I convinced someone,
my angel advisor, Susan Fiske,
然后我说服了一个人，
我的天使顾问苏珊·菲斯克（Susan Fiske）
to take me on,
and so I ended up at Princeton,
来接受我，
所以我最终来到了普林斯顿大学，
and I was like,
I am not supposed to be here.
我当时想，
我不应该在这里。
I am an impostor.
我是个骗子。 在
And the night before my first-year talk,
我第一年演讲的前一天晚上，
and the first-year talk at Princeton
is a 20-minute talk to 20 people.
以及在普林斯顿大学的第一年演讲
是对 20 个人进行 20 分钟的演讲。
That's it.
就是这样。
I was so afraid of being
found out the next day
我很害怕
第二天被发现，
that I called her
and said, "I'm quitting."
所以我打电话给她
说：“我要辞职了。”
She was like, "You are not quitting,
她说，“你不会放弃，
because I took a gamble
on you, and you're staying.
因为我在你身上下了赌注
，而你要留下来。
You're going to stay, and this is
what you're going to do.
你要留下来，这就是
你要做的。
You are going to fake it.
你会假装它。
You're going to do every talk
that you ever get asked to do.
你 你会做每
一次被要求做的演讲，
You're just going to do it
and do it and do it,
even if you're terrified
and just paralyzed
即使你感到害怕
、瘫痪
and having an out-of-body experience,
并有灵魂出窍的经历，你也会做、做、做，
until you have this moment where you say,
'Oh my gosh, I'm doing it.
直到。 你有这样的时刻，你会说，
‘天哪，我正在这么做。
Like, I have become this.
I am actually doing this.'"
’”
So that's what I did.
所以我就是这么做的。
Five years in grad school,
在研究生院读了五年，
a few years, you know,
I'm at Northwestern,
几年，你知道，
我在西北大学，
I moved to Harvard, I'm at Harvard,
我搬到了哈佛，我在哈佛，
I'm not really thinking about it anymore,
but for a long time I had been thinking,
我不再真正考虑它了，
但很长一段时间我一直在想，
"Not supposed to be here."
“不应该在这里。”
So at the end of my first year at Harvard,
因此，在我在哈佛的第一年结束时，一个
a student who had not talked
in class the entire semester,
整个学期都没有在课堂上说话的学生走进了我的办公室，
who I had said, "Look, you've gotta
participate or else you're going to fail,"
我曾对他说：“听着，你必须
参加，否则你就会失败。”
came into my office.
I really didn't know her at all.
。
我真的根本不认识她。
She came in totally defeated,
and she said,
她完全失败了，
她说：
"I'm not supposed to be here."
“我不应该在这里。”
And that was the moment for me.
那就是我的时刻。
Because two things happened.
因为发生了两件事。
One was that I realized,
一是我意识到，
oh my gosh,
I don't feel like that anymore.
天哪，
我不再有那样的感觉了。
I don't feel that anymore,
but she does, and I get that feeling.
我不再有这种感觉了，
但她有，而且我有这种感觉。
And the second was,
she is supposed to be here!
第二个是，
她应该在这里！
Like, she can fake it, she can become it.
就像，她可以假装它，她可以成为它。
So I was like, "Yes, you are!
You are supposed to be here!
所以我说，“是的，你是！
你应该在这里！
And tomorrow you're going to fake it,
明天你会假装它，
you're going to make yourself
powerful, and, you know --
你会让自己变得
强大，而且，你知道 -
(Applause)
（掌声）
And you're going to go
into the classroom,
而你是
走进教室，
and you are going to give
the best comment ever."
你就会给出
有史以来最好的评论。”
You know? And she gave
the best comment ever,
你知道？ 她给出了
有史以来最好的评论，
and people turned around and were like,
人们转过身来，说，
oh my God, I didn't even notice her
sitting there. (Laughter)
天哪，我什至没有注意到她
坐在那里。  （笑声）
She comes back to me months later,
几个月后她回到我身边，
and I realized that she had not just
faked it till she made it,
我意识到她不仅仅是在
成功之前假装它，而是在她真正
she had actually faked it
till she became it.
成功之前一直假装它。
So she had changed.
所以她变了。
And so I want to say to you,
don't fake it till you make it.
所以我想对你说，
在你成功之前不要假装它。
Fake it till you become it.
假装它直到你成为它。
Do it enough until you actually
become it and internalize.
做得足够多，直到你真正
成为它并内化为止。
The last thing I'm going
to leave you with is this.
我要留给你的最后一件事
就是这个。
Tiny tweaks can lead to big changes.
微小的调整可能会带来巨大的变化。
So, this is two minutes.
所以，这是两分钟。
Two minutes, two minutes, two minutes.
两分钟，两分钟，两分钟。
Before you go into the next stressful
evaluative situation,
在你进入下一个有压力的
评估情境之前，
for two minutes, try doing this,
in the elevator,
花两分钟时间，
在电梯里、
in a bathroom stall, at your desk
behind closed doors.
在浴室隔间里、在
紧闭门后的办公桌前尝试这样做。
That's what you want to do.
这就是你想做的。
Configure your brain
to cope the best in that situation.
配置你的大脑
以在这种情况下最好地应对。
Get your testosterone up.
Get your cortisol down.
让你的睾丸激素升高。
让你的皮质醇下降。
Don't leave that situation feeling
like, oh, I didn't show them who I am.
不要让这种情况
感觉，哦，我没有向他们展示我是谁。
Leave that situation feeling like,
让这种情况感觉就像，
I really feel like I got to say
who I am and show who I am.
我真的觉得我必须说出
我是谁并展示我是谁。
So I want to ask you first, you know,
both to try power posing,
所以我想首先请你
尝试摆姿势，
and also I want to ask you to share
the science, because this is simple.
我也想请你分享
科学知识，因为这很简单。
I don't have ego involved in this.
(Laughter)
我没有自我参与其中。
（笑声）
Give it away. Share it with people,
把它送给别人。 与人分享，
because the people who can use it the most
因为最能利用它的人
are the ones with no resources
and no technology
是那些没有资源
、没有技术
and no status and no power.
、没有地位、没有权力的人。
Give it to them
because they can do it in private.
把它交给他们，
因为他们可以私下做。
They need their bodies,
privacy and two minutes,
他们需要自己的身体、
隐私和两分钟，
and it can significantly change
the outcomes of their life.
这可以显着改变
他们的生活结果。
Thank you.
谢谢。
(Applause)
（掌声）